Peace be upon you, my Bey.
I came back to the lands you conquered, my Bey.
I must have a dark fate, since I
am praying at your grave and...
...I live your pain inside me.
I couldn't see you one more time
with my eyes in this world, but...
Your son Osman
...realized your dreams on
the lands where you came
with a few men and
established a blessed state.
I know I will see you in his face.
May your soul find peace.
May you rest well in your grave, my Bey.
Aameen.
Come on Alps!
Osman!
Before my blood dries,
I will spill yours, Osman.
They are behind us. We don't have much time.
Thanks to Allah, we kept our
promise and saved the Beys.
We will get out of this forest.
My Bey, our Alps wait ahead,
but we are not more than a dozen.
These dogs have many men.
The bigger they come, the
harder they fall. Don't worry.
Now I think about which one's head I will take.
It's the sound of hoofs. They are here, my Bey.
Boran.
You will go to the black forest in the north.
Make the preparations.
If we can't deal with them,
we will bring them to your place.
As you order my Bey.
Don't worry.
Let's go, we will go into
the forest from this side.
Okay my Bey.
Osman entered the forest.
You set this trap, Claudius.
You used the Beys as bait
and lured Osman into the trap.
Do you think Osman came with two Alps?
Do you think I didn't notice
Osman was luring us into a trap?
But I will ruin his trap.
Don't ever make the mistake
of underestimating your enemy.
Would you risk your life and threw yourself
into fire for a commander you met two days ago?
Look, Osman threw himself into the fire.
Don't worry, I don't underestimate him.
I even see him as my equal.
This excites me a lot.
Excellent.
I also like fighting such an enemy and winning.
They went into the forest.
Let's follow the tracks.
Kismet, you take Sofia and
Halime and go to the tribe.
Alps will come with you.
Sofia is entrusted to you.
Tell Osman Bey the situation,
alright? And I will go after Alaeddin.
Kismet Hatun, I don't want to owe her.
They must help her survive.
Mother, I will come with you.
No, daughter, I can't put you in danger.
You go with Sofia.
I won't leave my brother alone.
I made a mistake by escaping the tribe.
Let me make up for my mistake.
Halime.
Let me have the honour to
stand before my family, mother.
Didn't you say we will never be apart again?
Then wherever you go, I go.
Look at you...
Alright then. Come on.
My Bey.
Aykurt
What's the situation?
We're readying the traps, my Bey.
However, we do not have enough equipment.
We don't have many alps as well.
We only need a handful of alps.
Do not worry.
The number of jackals does not fear a wolf.
Even if it is fire coming
towards us, we will put it out.
Come on alps, get ready.
As you command, my Bey.
The attackers must be scouts!
Their encampment must be near!
Alps, check everywhere!
We will find them.
We have to find them.
My Shahzade.
My Shahzade, are you alright?
Cerkutay Bey.
I've done wrong to Alaeddin.
I was going to prevent
him from leaving the tribe.
Now, because of me..
Because of me, they are in Kucar's hand now.
My Shahzade.
Falling back was my idea.
There is a way for falling
back also, Cerkutay Bey.
He is a Shahzade.
He should've taken his precautions.
One mistake he makes..
..is good for the enemy..
..and terrible for alps.
However, still..
..me hitting him..
Cerkutay Bey.
Olcaytu must want..
He would want to kill them to make things even.
We need to find them.
We will.
We will, God willing.
Mistakes will be turned right.
Hearts will unite again, God willing.
God willing.
However, if something happens to them..
..then..
..I won't forgive myself.
They covered their tracks,
however, no holding back now!
We will find them!
Mother.
Yes?
Aren't you mad at me for
running away from the tribe?
Let's find your brother first.
Maybe I will be.
Do you remember what I told you?
There is a good in every mistake.
If you hadn't ran away
and fell in Begum's hands..
..we wouldn't have learned about your
brother and Gonca being held, right?
You're right, mother.
Come on then.
Come on, show me your skills.
Halime Hatun.
Mother.
You are a mother you can forgive.
What about my brothers?
My father?
They will get really mad at me.
After learning that I ran away.
Look here
When you see your father and brother..
..look at them as you do now..
..open your arms..
..and hug them like this.
Then, they will forgive you.
Is it that easy?
Of course.
However, we need to find
your brother first. Come on.
Mother.
We've found a track,
even if it's not my brother.
That is of Mogol.
That way.
Come on!
Come, come...
Alps, release the arrows!
My Bey, that dog Claudius is not among them.
I'm here, Osman!
I'm right here!
You thought I didn't understand
the trap you've set for us.
We are the hunters now.
Is that so?
My Bey, we're surrounded. What will we do?
Then..
..I will put..
..both of you in the same grave.
Attack!
Boran, we're falling back.
Osman!
You have no place to run! Come here!
Stop already!
Your efforts were deserving of
applause. However, this is the end.
Do not worry.
We always have a road to go.
We do not fall into desolation.
We never give up!
Stubbornnes, Osman!
You are only stubborn!
You saved the beys with
this stubbornnes as well!
You know your enemy well!
I am stubborn.
And I never give up!
Know this!
I never come to the field with a single trap.
You are stepping on the second one.
Attack!
Ya Allah!
Shield wall!
Those who play with wolves
bound to fall into a trap like a dog.
These dogs just keep coming.
Their death is near.
Come on, to horses.
Come on!
Move!
Osman!
I swear I will live for this!
I swear to you, I will live for this!
I swear to you!
I will live for this!
You dogs!
Let go!
You will wait..
..Orlok Kucar in here.
He will make you pay for your disrespect.
Put them into cages!
Increase security.
Not a bird will fly!
Five guards will watch them.
kill you.
I'll kill you
Let go!
Don't touch me.
Alaeddin
Maybe my father thinks we've arrived.
What will we do?
How will we escape from here?
They will do everything to not let us escape.
They will.
Kucar.
He will give me to Olcaytu to settle things.
Now, these dogs won't leave our side.
My Gonca.
It is me that they want.
I won't allow you to be harmed.
Never.
Alaeddin.
Alaeddin, they will kill you.
Don't be sad, dear.
No, Alaeddin.
Hatun.
..won't let them say the son
of Osman Bey died in a cell.
No matter what happens..
..I will walk to martyrdom with a fight.
What is her condition, Ulgen?
It was close to her stomach.
She wouldn't have survived otherwise.
She shouldn't have.
We will not be sad for this snake.
Fatma.
She guarded Halime.
We will at least show mercy.
Right?
Poena.
I won't show no mercy, aunt.
Who knows what is my brother
and Gonca is doing right now?
Am I supposed to think
about this spoiled thing now?
There is good in every evil, Fatma.
Besides, we could've ran off to
save Alaeddin and Gonca this way.
That trickster goes after my brother even.
What if I never see my brother again?
You will.
Of course you will.
not worry.
They will return to the tribe alive and well.
Poena.
We came to the frontiers
to fight the infidels with him.
Now what is he doing, Koca Bey?
If Osman Bey made an alliance with
that sinister Sofia, he must have a reason.
The blood of our people was
spilled by that infidel's sword.
He is a Bey. I would say
he knows the best, but no.
This is a different matter, Koca Bey.
Hasan Bey, if we fought the infidels once,
Osman Bey fought them a thousand times.
He knows what to do very well.
A Bey must stay calm in such times.
He must be patient, Hasan Bey.
Now what we must do is
not complain like the people.
We must stand tall next to our Bey.
Come, listen to this old companion of yours.
My Shahzade.
You took one of your children,
but I still have the other one, Bala.
I swear I will make you suffer in pain.
Demon.
Traitor.
She is still serving the Mongols like a dog.
My Shahzade.
Let's go and deal with that
witch who has nine lives.
No.
The ones with her are Kucar's loyal dogs.
So the witch called Begum
started working with Kucar.
Now we have the chance.
Now we will follow them...
...and enter their nest.
My Osman Bey.
Did they treat your wounds?
Are you feeling better?
The real cure for our wounds...
...is your victorious return from
Claudius and Kucar's nest, my Bey.
You resisted Claudius well.
I need Beys like you on my side.
Thank you.
Who else do you want to
see on your side, Osman Bey?
What happened, Hasan Bey?
Say it directly.
I mean that Hatun you made your ally.
The infidel Sofia who has
martyr blood on her hands.
Osman Bey.
Are you going to unite us with her?
Hasan Bey.
How will we explain this to my father, Fatma?
Know your limits.
Do you think the blood of our
martyrs and their lost lives...
Do you think we never think or plan anything?
Osman Bey...
What reason can make
a Turk ally with an infidel?
When you pledged loyalty to us...
...did you come here only
to fight with your sword?
Our cause is not just about being victorious.
We are ruling a state here, a state.
We are leading a path for the people.
But sometimes, for future victories...
...we know we should make sacrifices.
Such sacrifice must never be made.
Hasan Bey.
Koca Bey.
Wait. Finish your words.
I did not come to the frontiers to
unite with the infidels, Osman Bey.
Turn back from this mistake.
Turn back or else..
-No "or else".
I won't entrust the state or the nation
to someone who questions a Bey's word.
Hasan Bey.
May your path be clear.
All the Beys who are on the way...
...to come to the frontiers to pledge
allegiance to you will hear this, Osman Bey.
Koca Bey..
If you think like Hasan Bey
May you go safely as well then.
You too, Beys.
I bowed this head to you
so you could be my leader.
I would give up my head for your
path without question, my Bey.
Hasan wants the same thing as well.
But I couldn't understand why he did this.
My own brother Yigit Bey is among
those who are coming to pledge allegiance.
He won't listen to Hasan.
We never force anyone to pledge allegiance.
If someone wants to leave the path...
...they do it by their own choice.
But know this...
Our path will always be for gaza and conquest.
If anyone doubts this, they will have
no place beside me or in my state.
Everyone must know this.
In both west and east, enemies
make alliances against us.
Now, we will see these
frontiers as our hunting ground.
The fire of conquest will
burn so strongly that...
...it will be seen even beyond the borders.
We will burn the infidels
and the cruel ones alive.
Yes my Bey.
Here is my command.
We will hold a council.
Koca Bey, send word to all the
Beys under my rule and in my land.
I want to see them all at this great council.
As you order my Bey.
Father...
Fatma.
Where is your mother?
Halime left the tribe.
My mother is after her.
Alaeddin.
Brother..
Kucar...
I will show you that a Kayi
will never be a prisoner.
Kucar is not here, my Shahzade.
He is not here, but his precautions are strict.
Even getting close is enough to be exposed.
If we make one mistake, everyone
in the quarters will draw their swords.
Beys.
What are the legends of our ancestors for?
The soul of Kurshad, who raided the Chinese
palace with forty soldiers, is with us.
Now, with that same faith and goal...
.we will destroy this.
...nest of looters.
Shamil. Kanyumaz. Take Alps with you and...
Inform Osman Bey.
My Shahzade, we cannot leave you alone.
We needed you here so you
could go and inform Osman Bey.
Go quickly now.
As you order my Shahzade.
Kucar's men were behind her.
Begum...
...works for Kucar, Osman Bey.
Begum..
How long will you keep
trying to make me kill you, huh?
She touched my Poena...
I will kill her.
Begum is not the only ally of Kucar.
There is someone else.
I am talking about Claudius.
Claudius..
Did he ally with Kucar who set his
eyes on Bursa? This is ridiculous.
I would never believe that.
He would of course ally with him to rule Bursa.
You are surprised by this but not
surprised that fate brought us together?
Dastard.
So, you betrayed the Emperor.
You betrayed me once again.
Osman Bey.
Their alliance is a big threat to us.
You must prevent this immediately.
My first duty is to protect my children.
Olcaytu asked for a daughter
and a son for retaliation...
...and now their lives are at risk.
You said you spoke with Kucar to take Bursa.
Do you know where he is?
If you tell me where he is, I
can find Alaeddin and Gonca.
I did not go there. Kucar came to Bursa.
I don't know where he is.
I wish I did.
Osman Bey...
Find Poena.
Don't let something happen to her.
Her name is Halime.
Even if you try to poison her,
she is with her mother now.
She is after her family and her brother.
You will never be able to break this bond.
Poena.
I won't let you slip away from my hands.
What is she doing here?
Alaeddin Bey.
And his precious Hatun.
Thanks to me, you finally
got what you deserved, huh?
You treacherous snake.
You keep serving the Mongols like a dog, huh?
You served Ulugan first...
After him..
Did you sell your honour to Kucar?
Are you the Kayi, those who lack honor?
You drew my Yusuf to your side..
..pushing him to the front at every battle..
..and finally took his life.
He didn't choose treachery like you!
Yusuf Bey's place..
..is the sacred stop of our martyrs.
Do not worry.
You and your sister will share the same place.
My sister?
I am talking about Halime.
You and your sister will die..
..at the hands of Olcaytu in the end.
You devil!
So Kucar hired you to kidnap Halime!
Don't you have any honor, Begum?
Separating a child from her
family befits no honor!
If you harm my sister in any way..
..I will keep the promise I made
when you pushed my father into flame.
I swear, I won't kill you.
But you will be begging to die.
My brother.
Grows enmity towards me.
He left this World.
You don't have the words to scare me now.
Besides, from what I've heard..
..you found what you deserve.
You became enemies with Orhan Bey.
Everyone finds what they deserve in the end.
Shut it!
Look here!
Look at me!
I am warning you one last time, hatun.
If you..
..harm any of my kin..
..I will make this world
hell for you. Know that well.
Don't make me laugh, Alaeddin Bey.
In this condition?
Come on, alps.
We're leaving.
You laugh.
Go ahead.
You won't be laughing soon.
Trouble finds us.
We laugh at times..
..but we weep at the heart.
A Bey must have a heart of iron to stay strong.
That sorrow is what keeps us alive.
Traitors always have tricks up their sleeves.
However, it is about..
..staying strong..
..uniting and not falling.
We will.
We will rise for the World of Islam..
..and we won't allow these dogs..
..who suck the blood of
innocent for worldly treasures..
..and invaders of these lands.
It is time, Cerkutay Bey.
These dogs are leaving also.
May you strike fast.
Will we attack the encampment without Osman Bey?
Kucar is not here.
His warriors are leaving.
There will not be a better time to attack.
We need to sneak inside..
..and deal with this.
What if I get caught?
Samil and alps..
..will surely send word to Osman Bey.
I was searching for someone more mad than me..
..since Bamsi Bey gave me this sword.
However, I finally found it.
Tell me, my Shahzade.
What do you have in mind?
Follow me.
Nilufer, Fatma.
Take care of the tribe.
Don't worry, father.
Father.
I do not..
..trust that girl.
I fear something will happen to mother.
You take care of yourself too, alright?
My daughter, what are you saying?
Are you talking about Halime?
There won't be such a thing.
She is your kind.
She is with your mother.
She is fighting for the tribe, can't you see?
Don't do this.
Father, I can not stomach what she did.
She is of our blood,
however, her soul is not of us.
Fatma.
Don't you say that.
I will not hear something like
this from you again, alright?
I won't allow disunion in this tribe.
Look here.
I won't allow it.
Alright, Fatma?
Nilufer.
Sofia will not leave her tent no matter what.
Do not keep your eyes off of her.
As you command, father.
Fatma.
Come on, alps.
Come on!
Kucar did not lose any time, Hatun.
He assigned the most
vile one to kidnap my sister.
They couldn't succeed for now, however..
..if this remains as their intention..
..Halime will not be safe, Alaeddin.
The heart just united with it's longing.
What Begum did..
I wonder if my mother is worried now.
If she saw what we're like now.
Her heart must be burning.
No.
We will not let..
..my mother and my father feel this pain.
Neither we nor my sister.
We will not be captives of these dogs.
We will not be.
Alaeddin.
Orhan Bey...
-Yes?
He must've heard our situation, Hatun
He found our tracks.
Your brother did not leave you, Alaeddin.
Yes.
How will they take them out?
With our help.
I will get you out.
Come.
Brother.
May you prosper, brother.
So, the dogs of Osman gathers in our camp!
You dogs.
Your efforts are for naught!
You will not escape!
Surrender!
When did we ever surrender?
Hatun, you will escape in the first clash.
I won't leave. I won't
leave you alone, Alaeddin.
You will go and bring help.
I will go. However, I will get
help and come back at once.
Alright.
Be careful.
You too.
Nokers!
(Mongolian Soldiers)
Attack!
Come on, hatun.
Warriors!
Take them out!
I will butcher you all!
I will let wolves feast on your dead bodies!
I swear!
Bring the sons of Osman to the cage.
Take this used-to-be mongol with them.
Kucar will decide on his fate when he arrives.
Two of you, go after the running hatun.
Come on, take them!
If they won't give us Bursa..
..then kill them all.
Loyal servants..
..of beautiful Bursa.
Because Sofia..
..has joined the enemy..
..her days have ended!
However, do not worry!
I will save you..
..from this pitiful..
..situation you are in..
..and bring Bursa to it's former glory!
We will do it together!
We will bring..
..then end of Turks together!
You..
..stood against..
..the Emperor, Claudius.
That is rebellion.
And the penalty..
..is death!
We will not serve you!
Hristo?
I gave you a chance to live.
However, you do not deserve it.
Besides, to hell with that
Emperor that you love so much!
Kill them all!
Stop!
Or you die.
Come and try then.
Come on!
Stop!
She is done.
Come on.
Mother..
..a horse rider is coming.
Stay alert!
Halime, stay behind me.
Gonca?
Gonca!
My daughter!
Hold on!
Come!
Hold on! Hold her!
Hold her!
My daughter!
Slowly.
My Gonca, are you alright?
Hold her!
My daughter, hang tight!
Hang tight!
Come on, In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
It's over, Gonca.
Gonca, look at me.
My daughter, are you alright? Bring water!
Are you alright?
Give it here.
Lift her up!
Here.
Gonca.
Open your eyes, daughter.
Look at me.
Where were they keeping you?
What happened?
Alaeddin.
Orhan Bey.
Orhan came after you, yes.
He fell captive.
What?
Gonca, where are they keeping him?
Where are they keeping the sons, Gonca?
Where are they keeping them?
Gonca, open your eyes! Open your eyes!
Alps!
Ready the horse!
Gulce take Gonca to the tribe!
Come on, lift her up!
Come on!
Lift her up!
Come on.
Cerkutay Bey.
You are alright, right?
I am alright, my Shahzade, I am, but...
Once I kill Kucar's men I will feel even better.
The time will come for that.
My Allah..
Help my Hatun, my Allah...
May You clear the path that my
rose Gonca is on from evil, my Allah.
Alaeddin..
Brother...
Gonca is very good at riding horses.
She must have already flown
to the tribe like the wind, huh?
She must have, right?
Yes, she must have.
God willing she ran away and saved her life.
She won't be able to escape!
Soon, my nokers will bring her head to me!
Don't!
Don't you dare hurt my Hatun!
Your fates have united as well.
Don't worry.
You will never be separated again.
Kucar.
You never understand, huh?
You never see what is going to happen.
This situation of us...
...will not bring you victory...
...but death. Death.
Osman Bey's furor will
burn your heart in flames.
You'll see.
Osman... Osman...
...now thinks he is playing a game against me...
...after he notices your absence, he will
be devastated and he will understand that...
...Kucar played the biggest game!
Mankurt..
Make sure you don't forget giving...
...water and food to the Beys here.
We need them.
What about this Mongol defector?
What about him?
Did he say that to me?
He will kill you all!
Don't touch him!
...one of Osman's...
...daughters for retaliation and go to Tabriz...
...this one will come with us as well.
Our Khan will make him pay for betraying us.
Gonca.
Gonca, my daughter.
She is badly injured.
My daughter...
Can you speak? Alaeddin..
Where is Alaeddin?
Kucar... You took Alaeddin..
...now you will never find peace in this world.
Tell me!
Where are Bala and Halime tracking from?
We parted ways at Kizilcinar, my Bey.
They were going to track beyond that point.
Is that so?
Do not make Gonca wait here
any longer. To the tribe! Immediately!
Go!
Alps!
We are going to Kizilcinar.
Bring me the horse!
Bursa now belongs to us!
Kill everyone who resists!
From now on, every border in these lands...
...will be drawn by the tip of my sword.
A new era is beginning in Bursa.
Bring me the head of traitor Hristo.
Right away.
My Allah, may You protect my children.
Protect them from the evilness
of enemies and from all troubles.
May You surround each of their
steps with Your mercy and protection.
Do not let us fall into separation, my Allah.
Make us complete.
You are the One Who wants reunions.
May You bring us together as well.
Aameen.
Aameen mother. Aameen.
Every time you say "mother"
my heart beats so differently.
Come here, come.
I don't know why, but...
...every time I say "mother"
I want to say it more.
Say it, my daughter. Say it as much as you want.
Let's make up for the years we've lost, huh?
Come.
I used to be sad thinking I had no one.
But it was all in vain.
Were those years hard for you, my daughter?
No.
I didn't say it to make you sad, mother.
Even though Sofia did evil things
to us, she was always good to me.
She never tortured me.
Poena!
Sofia!
Today, when she threw herself
in front of you, I believed her.
But I won't forget the evilness she
did. The time for revenge will come.
Mother..
Will my brothers make peace?
They are very close to each other, my daughter.
If they can sit and talk face to face, it
will be solved, but they are stubborn.
They are stubborn, my daughter.
Then..
...when we find my brother
Alaeddin, let's lock them in somewhere.
Look, you thought of this
well. Maybe we can try it.
My daughter.
My dear daughter.
Bala Hatuns fought here.
They went this way.
But they can't go any further at night.
Surely... They will surely wait somewhere.
What should we do, my Bey? What is your order?
We will wait until tomorrow
morning to follow the right track.
Remove these corpses.
Set the fire here. Place a few Alps around.
If you allow me, I want to name him Alaeddin.
Sure.
Alaeddin Ali
My Alaeddin.
How could you accept Alaeddin leaving?
How could you be silent?
How could you let him go?
I didn't accept anything.
He said he wanted to go.
And I let him go.
My Alaeddin Ali.
I will break the jaw of
anyone who sharpens their teeth
against my children,
my family, or my nation.
Don't worry.
I will not leave you in the hands of those dogs.
I will take you from them, Alaeddin.
I will take you, my son.
With that punch you threw, I thought...
...I no longer had a brother.
I thought my brother would
never talk to me again.
But..
...without knowing that I was captured...
...you sensed that my life was
in danger and came right away.
What else could I have done, brother?
How could I leave you to
the mercy of those dastards?
Tell me.
If it were you, wouldn't you have done the same?
I would have.
If the mountains stood in front of me, I
would destroy them all and come to you.
I would sacrifice my life
to protect yours, brother.
You would.
Sure you would.
I, Alaeddin...
...after my father, I trust only you in
this world. I lean my back only to you.
But I was defeated by my anger.
I parted ways.
I turned my back on you, brother.
No.
You are not the only one...
...who was defeated by his anger, my brother.
Just because we had a conflict...
...should not have thrown that punch at you.
You turned your back on us. You left.
But I am responsible for this, my brother.
I broke your heart.
No.
If hearts are broken, they
are broken mutually, brother.
I also said things I shouldn't have to you.
You are older than me. So forgive me, alright?
I would give a thousand lives for you.
You forgive me too, my brother.
Forgive me too.
My lion brother.
Look at you...
These are the children of Dark Osman.
The brotherhood that brings
the entire world to its knees...
...that makes the enemy..
...bow down.
She lost too much blood.
Ulgen sister...
What if the medicine doesn't work?
It will.
Don't think of bad things, Fatma.
She is waking up.
Aunt.
Gonca.
You scared us all.
Are you alright?
Alaeddin.
Sofia told us, we know everything.
My mother is looking for him.
They will save Alaeddin, don't worry.
Aunt, do you remember where they kept him?
I don't know.
I don't know where they kept us.
Orhan came after you, didn't he?
He did.
Alright.
Don't tire yourself more.
Alaeddin...
...and Cerkutay, Orhan...
They all...
They are all...
They are all captured by Kucar.
My Allah, protect them.
What?
Alaeddin..
No.
I will go after my brothers.
I can't stay anymore. -Fatma.
Will go against my father's command?
Look.
Father and mother are after them.
They will rescue them.
Don't worry.
Sister.
If I am not with my father and mother..
..it is because of that girl.
Look.
While all of us suffer the same pain..
..don't wear yourself out like this.
Besides..
..she is your sister.
She is not my sister.
She proved me right by pushing me into that pit.
Now, all the lands are ours!
So you were going to escape to Osman.
There is no escaping from us!
Father!
Let go of my father!
Let go of the kid.
I told you to let him go.
Who are you, old man?
You can barely stand.
Go away, don't find your trouble here.
You will be punished..
..for this, old man
Come on.
We owe you our lives, stranger.
Who are you?
One of Osman Bey's soldiers,
whom you never question his justice.
Do you know Osman Bey?
I know him well.
Tell me, innkeeper.
Do you wish to go to Osman Bey..
..for the chaos going on in Bursa?
Bursa had no justice before as well.
With Ilhanids coming, it all went to chaos.
Only Osman Bey..
..can save us.
Do not worry.
I will take you to Osman Bey.
Thanks.
Go and prepare.
Come on.
My valiant Osman, you
fight against all infidels.
This duty you took..
..has even outgrown your fathers'.
There was one son of Bey, now there is two.
Here, come and eat.
Alaeddin Bey is used to our hospitality!
Say what you want to say.
However, don’t keep it long.
So now you've become "we" again.
The might of Mongols has united..
..two brothers that were against each other.
However, it is all for naught.
Do you think we have the
manners of a pig like you, Kucar?
There can be resentment.
However, brothers can not
have enmity against each other.
Only enemy to the Turks..
..are lowly tyrants like you.
Are you done?
You keep talking like this..
..however, if you hadn't
gotten into each other..
..you would escape the claws of the eagle.
Ilhanids..
..will rule the World..
..by seperating the likes of you!
Only Mongols..
..always got seperated, Kucar.
In the east, west..
..north, south.
Tell me.
How many states do you have there?
You must've forgotten.
Even our seperation is
enough to rule the whole world.
How many of you lost their heads
to come and conquer the borders?
Do not forget those.
So you will
..make the grand Ilhanids headless?
Take Byzantine as example, Kucar.
They used to talk like you, Kucar.
And now what happened?
Do you know?
Even our names alone..
..bring fear into their hearts.
For all these years..
..only one..
..or two brigades came to the borders.
Have you seen the power of Ilhanids?
We've received the news from Claudius.
Now, Bursa is..
..Ilhanid's land.
What do you mean?
What are you saying?
So..
..you think..
..all those Ilhanids armies
came to the borders for nothing?
..do you think I'm a simple messenger..
..or shortsighted like Ulugan?
..who made Bursa..
..Ilhanids land with politics
without picking up my sword..
..will not sheathe my sword..
..when..
..conquering..
..the Kayi Tribe.
We will demolish..
..your politics..
and your sword, Kucar!
We will demolish!
Now..
..you don't even own..
..your own life, let alone Bursa.
Know that well.
So the sons of a goat shepherd..
..threatens Ilhanids..
..with it's life, is that so?
I'll see..
..if you have the audacity..
..once I bring you all..
..to Olcaytu!
You will see.
Stand back, daughter.
Stand back!
Hucar's lair must be nearby.
Be careful!
We will find them, mother.
We will, daughter.
I'm coming my sons.
Check around.
Stand your guard!
Halime.
Stand back, daughter.
I won't leave you alone.
Be careful.
Attack!
Fights like a lion.
What is happening, my Bey?
No resting before I have my sons!
I will only take lives!
Bala!
Osman
Halime?
Halime!
My daughter.
Halime, are you alright?
I'm alright.
However..
..I won't be well..
..until my brothers are saved.
Orhan is at Kucar's hands as well, Osman Bey.
Bring that dog here!
Look..
Where is the nest of that dog Kucar?
Where?! Where is he keeping my children?
Stop. They are ahead. They are behind the hill.
Osman.
Let's save our sons before we suffer
from the grief of losing another child.
Don't worry.
We will save them all. We
will save them all. Don't worry.
Let's go get them.
Now..
So, you say Bursa joined the Ilkhanate
with Claudius' rebellion, my Shahzade.
And against the Emperor's order.
So Claudius opposed the
alliance because of this.
Claudius didn't come to the
frontiers to fight for his state, brother.
Even under the Mongols,
he only wanted to take Bursa.
My fear is that, my Shahzades...
Sofia, who gave up Halime
Hatun to protect Bursa...
She might do anything if
she loses Bursa, you'll say.
That is possible.
She might continue the alliance
with us to get Bursa back as well.
You are right, brother, you are right.
But now, what we must do is act carefully.
You know very well...
...what Bursa being ruled by Mongols...
...means to us, brother.
Huh, Cerkutay Bey?
We know, of course we know.
The dream that my father had all his
life, the dream we grew in our hearts...
This will make it more difficult
for us to realize that dream.
Bursa is the door to the road of
conquests that goes way beyond.
Bursa is the unique stop on
the way to the RedApple for us.
If the Ilkhanate...
...takes the city permanently...
..then..
...then that door...
...will never open for us again.
O, old times...
The day you were conquered
feels like yesterday, Sogut.
So many martyrs have
fallen on this land for you.
The day you raised your glorious
banner here feels like yesterday, my Bey.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too uncle.
I want one oke of this.
I'll weigh it right away, uncle.
How is the trade going here? They say
taxes are too heavy for the people here.
No, uncle.
We had difficulty during Mongol
cruelty, but now taxes are reduced by half.
What you heard is true in
Byzantine lands, stranger.
This is the land of Osman Bey.
It's clear he won the hearts
of both Turks and Greeks.
But I don't know him. Who is this Osman Bey?
Uncle, how can you not know Osman Bey...
...who is famous for his justice
and has conquered many places?
Where is your Bey now?
My Bey sent word to all the other Beys.
He will hold a conquest council in the tribe.
If you go to the tribe, maybe you can see him.
-Thank you.
Alps! Be careful, there might be a trap.
That's what happened, Yigit Bey.
Osman Bey betrayed the cause.
He works with the infidels who killed our men.
What hurts me the most is your brother Koca Bey.
He does not see what is happening.
He follows the wrong path of Osman Bey.
Hasan Bey, you cannot rest
in the shadow of an old tree.
Because you never know when it will fall.
I came here to invite you to a gathering.
What gathering is that? Who wants to see me?
Not only you, but all the Beys who came with me.
Orlok Kucar..
...is a cruel man who plants the seed
of evilness in the frontiers, Yigit Bey.
Do you also betray our way?
Never. The Beys want to see if
there is another way besides war.
But they will also see this effort is useless.
Does your brother know?
Not yet.
He will hear it when the time comes.
Come on!
Walk.
My Bey, Kucar...
Orhan and Alaeddin are in Kucar's hands.
Orhan Bey?
He was going to wait.
He sent us to inform you, my Bey.
He went there alone and
risked himself for his brother.
My Allah, don't take them from us.
We won't lose hope, don't worry.
One way or another, we will save them.
They won't hurt our family again.
Halime, come on, my daughter.
You are not coming with us. You
will return to the tribe with the Alps.
I don't want to go back, father.
My daughter, we can't throw
you into the fire. Go now.
If I leave your side, that's
when I fall into the fire.
Because of the days I
didn't get to live with you...
...I want to live every moment with you, my Bey.
Please let me be here with my family, my Bey.
Did you hear that, Osman Bey?
We are going to suffer because of her tongue.
She speaks so well and convinces us easily.
I wonder who she takes after.
I wonder who.
Anyway. My daughter.
But you will be careful, huh?
As you order my Bey.
Kucar's place looks like
an eagle's nest, my Bey.
My Bey, the precautions
at the quarters are strict.
No matter what, it doesn't matter to us.
As long as we have courage in
our hearts and swords in our hands...
...nothing can stop us.
They tested us with our children.
We will be death to them with our swords.
Allah is the Greatest.
Tell me everything is alright in Bursa, Hristo.
Claudius took over Bursa.
He also killed your loyal soldiers.
What are you saying?
I barely escaped.
Claudius..
After my father, now you betrayed me...
Bursa is mine!
I will never leave it!
Walk!
Fatma Hatun! This infidel Hatun wants to leave!
Alps!
You cannot keep me here.
It is the order of Osman Bey, Sofia.
Until he comes to the tribe,
you cannot take a step outside.
I am not Osman's subject.
I don't care about his order.
Come on, Hristo!
Sofia.
If we go there, we'll die
I will die!
But I won't stay here!
Move!
Clear the way!
Do not resist, Sofia.
Go to your tent.
Sisters will treat your wound.
Alps!
You take care of Hristo.
Let go.
Near Kucar Area
So you do your plans.
The sons..
..they never kneeled.
Do not worry.
Of course.
If they tried to chain them..
..they must've bite hard.
Halime, what are you doing?
Stand back.
What will we do, Osman Bey?
How will we rescue the sons from there?
We will, do not worry.
We will go around them.
Alps.
Follow me.
I've invited you as your elder.
And you responded..
..as a form of respect.
May you prosper.
Welcome.
Thank you.
By coming to me
..you chose peace, not war..
..you chose not bloodshed..
..but peace.
Everyone knows that..
..our ways and hearts..
..with beys are one.
We have not chosen anything yet, Kucar.
In these borders, that we
came to from a long way..
..we would like to..
..settle here.
However, we see that..
..all of our enemies..
..there..
..are on the same side.
While you promise peace to us..
..do you wish us to..
..be on the same side with our enemies?
Just because we didn't go to Osman Bey..
..and obeyed him, don't think
that we will embrace you, Kucar.
We will leave this place if needed, however..
..we will not obey you.
Boran.
My Bey.
Act fast with my shot.
We will ruin them.
Come then.
-Osman Bey.
-Father.
We will demolish this jackals' den.
They separated our sons from
us. And we will be their death.
Attack!
My Halime.
It is you, isn't it?
It is me, brother.
I'm Halime.
My dear, how I missed you.
Thank Allah, Who united us.
We will fight together now.
You look exactly like my
mother. You fight just like her.
Come on, follow me.
My children, are you alright?
The waiting was tiring, mother.
Now, we will butcher
these dogs and finally rest.
Mother!
Is Gonca alright?
She is alright!
She is at the tribe now.
Do not worry.
I am giving you the right to live.
I am giving you the chance of freedom.
You will see.
The power of the west..
..is in my hands.
The city of silk..
..the heart of trade, Bursa..
..is under my command!
Ilhanid Empire at the east..
..and it's servants..
..at the west..
..the soldiers of Byzantine.
Those who stay..
..between these two iron fists..
..have chosen death.
If you do business with Osman..
if you..
..even walk near him..
..you will all..
..face my wrath!
States are taken with swords.
However, the people
..can not be managed with sword.
We do not obey anyone!
-He is right.
-That's true!
I do not tell you to obey.
Owe your allegience!
So that I can share..
..the most important parts of these lands..
..the rivers, with you!
So that you can live..
..in your own land, freely.
Then, let us discuss this..
..with other beys.
Alright.
Wait for our response.
Orlok Kucar.
Ya Allah!
Strike them, valiants!
My sons.
My Bey.
I've brought shame to you by being captive.
I've brought my brother along with me.
It's my mistake.
Forgive me.
Brother.
My brother speaks true..
..however, he is missing the points.
We did this mistake together.
Forgive us, my Bey.
From now on, no matter what happens..
..we will not do the same mistake.
Shame suits those who fall
into despair. Do not be ashamed.
You..
..fought well.
May you prosper.
Stand tall.
..there is good in every mistake.
The infidel made you see the truth.
Do not stay seperated again
and upset my mother, alright?
Come here.
Come.
Look at what she's saying.
Yes, my Alaeddin.
She speaks plainly. She has a very sharp tongue.
So Halime will complete what Fatma shortfalls.
Now we're in trouble.
They will give us quite the trouble.
We have to endure it.
My Bey, that dog Kucar.
He was going to take us to Olcaytu..
..after capturing one of our sisters.
However, he is gone for a long time.
I wish he would come.
Our house is one now.
We are like a firm fist.
We will surely..
..punish for what he did.
What do you think, Osman Bey?
We can not leave here now.
We will spend the night here.
If Kucar comes..
..we will take his life, of course.
If he does not..
..we will take it later.
You did your duty well
during with the beys today.
Now you will have what you want.
However..
..use this chance well, Yigit Bey.
I will hone the beys slowly.
However, they all obey Osman.
They are as stubborn..
..to walk with him until death.
So you're saying that you can't.
It is difficult.
However, it won't escape my claws.
I will seperate beys one by one.
I will start from those who hate Osman first.
You're talking about those..
..who come from Osman's side.
Hasan Bey.
However..
..he hates Claudius.
I will seperate Osman from his beys also.
He will have nothing to stand on.
My daughter
What were you thinking?
How cute you are.
Mother.
We went with Gonca without a notice.
Your heart must've burned.
I thought that saying goodbye
like this would be easier.
Forgive me.
I forgive you, my Alaeddin.
I forgive you, my son.
You stay near me..
..and I'll erase all of your mistakes.
..seeing you all..
..like this..
..after all these years burns my heart more.
No, my daughter.
Think about the good days we will have.
Alright, my dear?
Just like my other children.
I escaped the tribe thinking you don't trust me.
While even I can not forgive what I've done..
..you've forgiven me.
So that's what it means..
..to be family.
Now I understand.
Of course.
Don't think about these now.
Because, no matter what happens..
..being family means staying together.
Your brother, sister, mother, whoever.
It means following after them all the time.
It means not leaving them alone.
So, Bala.
Our children.
Our children are here.
One other is right there.
And our brides are waiting us at the tribe.
My alps are with us as well.
My beys are with us too.
May you prosper, my Bey.
Thank Allah.
Is there blessing greater in this world?
No, my Bey.
We do not need more.
Father.
Father?
Mother.
Yes, dear?
Come here then.
Father, you said.
Father.
I thought about it a lot and made a decision.
What is it? Tell us.
Even though my sins have
taken me far from you...
...I don't want to be away from you anymore.
Like you..
..I want to believe in Allah Who makes
those who choose their path sinless...
...as if they were born again.
Hay Praise be.
Thanks to my Allah...
...Who created you and granted you to us.
Thanks to Him.
My beautiful daughter.
My Halime.
My mother's name...
You filled our hearts with joy.
The dear one of her mother...
I can't get enough of hugging you.
Now..
...you will repeat after me.
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah..
worthy of worship except Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammad
is His servant and Messenger.
Just as your return and our reunion,
may it be blessed, my daughter.
Aameen.
Aameen my Bey.
Wait.
Look.
This was a gift from your father.
I used to hug this when you were gone.
Now it's my gift to you, my daughter.
Bless your salvation, God willing.
That's how it works. The water
of truth always finds its way.
As long as our hearts are full of faith and
our cause is always the way of The Righteous...
...this water will surely find its way.
And we will always be the ones who
reach happiness on the path of conquest.
God willing my Bey.
Welcome Osman Bey!
Long live Osman Bey!
Thank you, live long.
Live long.
Welcome, my Bey.
They wanted your state and they were destroyed.
They wanted your child
and were defeated, my Bey.
Long live Osman Bey!
O, my people!
My Beys, my sisters!
Thanks to my Allah, we returned
victorious to our tribe again.
Know this..
Victory belongs only to those who believe
and whose hearts burn with the fire of faith.
Long live Osman Bey!
Welcome Osman Bey!
Thank you.
My Alaeddin!
My Hatun..
My dear Gonca...
You were wounded while running
away. Are you alright, my Hatun?
I am alright, I am alright.
You came back safely. Scholar...
It no longer hurts...
Thanks to Allah...
My Hatun... My Hatun...
Thanks to Allah, I came together with you.
Thanks to Allah Who gave you, our child...
...and my siblings to me.
My Fatma
Thanks to Allah...
I kept waiting for you, I was so afraid.
We returned, my Fatma. We returned.
We saved your brothers
with your sister and returned.
Thank you.
All the Beys are waiting for you.
They are all ready, my Bey.
Thanks, thanks.
O, Ertugrul Ghazi's Dark Osman.
Praise be to you.
Attention!
Osman Bey the ruler of the state!
Are the preparations complete, Koca Bey?
As you ordered, my Bey.
Do not let anyone into the council.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too my Bey!
I open our council with
Almighty Allah's 99 names
Who holds us responsible
for effort, not victory.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Kayi's brave Beys...
...honest Beys.
We organized a council and invited you.
You did not reject and came here. Thank you.
If you are the one inviting, we will
come running no matter what, my Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
The council we hold today...
...is the sign of the tough
battle we will face tomorrow.
What a blessed news this is!
What a blessed news this is, Osman Bey!
This heart keeps burning for that battle.
We heard that..
...the jackal and hyena have united.
And they settled in Bursa, our target.
But they don't know that...
...the wolf never sleeps...
...on a cold night.
Is our first target Bursa, my Bey?
Bursa is always our target.
It is the goal in our hearts.
But the moves we make in this war
will bring us closer to Bursa step by step.
Now our first target is the Ilkhanid army
coming from Enguru to these frontiers.
And the soldiers of Claudius
who want to unite with them.
We will never allow our enemies
to unite and come upon us.
We will ruin them! We will destroy them!
We will place the Akinji
tribes who come to pledge
allegiance on the lands we
will conquer and take from them.
And so we will slowly spread around Bursa.
This is...
...such a conquest that...
...not only the Alps...
...but also the young valiants
whose mustaches are just growing...
...and the elderly who can still hold swords...
All of them...
All of them will become soldiers for this cause.
This..
This will be such a war that..
It will be the bloodiest war...
...these lands have ever witnessed.
The blows we will strike against our enemies...
..in the east..
..the west..
..at the frontiers, beyond the frontiers...
...will be the moves of the
conquest that will change the order.
This sword which is drawn from its sheath...
...will not be put back into its sheath...
...until it brings justice and
order to these frontiers and lands.
The steps we take today...
...will spread like...
...an avalanche across this land.
Allah is the Greatest!
Who sent it?
It is brought by Byzantine Emperor Andronikos'
personal messenger, my Bey.
The emperor invites us to Iznik.